nutritionforest.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy – Nutrition Forest

### Privacy Policy

Every individual has a right to privacy and Nutrition Forest deeply respects this right of all its customers. Our relationship with all our customers is very intrinsic and the most valuable asset which helps to take our reputation to the high stature. We believe that smooth and strong relationship with customers can turn a product into a brand.

We understand the importance of private information whether it’s related to finance or your contact details. When you place an order via online payment, we don’t reveal your personal information or account details to anyone.  

We reserve the right to disclose or report personal information in limited circumstances where we believe in good faith that disclosure is required under law, to co-operate with regulators or law enforcement authorities, or to protect our rights or property. We use personal information in ways that are compatible with purposes for which we originally requested it. For example, we use your information to process your requests and transactions, to provide you with additional information about products and services and all this can be carried out when information is shared with agent who ensures these information will be kept strictly confidential.

It is also to be noted that we collect the necessary information of our customers to administer our business smoothly and deliver satisfactory services. It can also include advising you about our products and other offers or schemes that we believe may interest you.

In order to provide you better services, we may combine your information on the Web or through other channels. When we share personal information with shipping company, we protect your personal and financial information with a strict agreement of confidentiality. Companies, that we hire to provide the best services to our customers, act as our agent must conform to our privacy standards.

Nutrition Forest corporate policies require that employees with access to confidential customer information don’t use or disclose the information except for business use. All employees are required to safeguard such information, as specified in their agreement of confidentiality with Nutrition Forest. In any circumstance, if you receive any invitation to buy a product or a service from any company not affiliated with Nutrition Forest, you can drop a request to decline such kind of offers or invitations. In all cases your personal information is protected by a strict agreement of confidentiality.

We do not allow any non affiliated company to retain your personal information longer than necessary to provide the product, service, or information, unless you grant us permission to do so. We continue to evaluate our efforts to protect personal information and make every effort to keep your details accurate and up to date. If you identify any error in your personal information or need to make a change to that information, please contact us and we will promptly update our records. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us by e-mail at support @ nutritionforestDOTcom

### Internet Cookies

To personalize your experience on our website or with one of our promotions, we may assign your computer browser a unique random number, called a "cookie." Cookies enhance the Nutrition Forest web site performance in several important ways: they personalize your experience on our site, and they make your visit to our site more convenient for you. Your privacy and security are not compromised when you accept a cookie from our website.

We do not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies can't read data from your computer's hard disk or read cookie files from other Web sites. In addition, companies we may hire to evaluate our Web promotions may set cookies to assist with such an evaluation. Again, neither Nutrition Forest nor companies acting on our behalf use cookies to collect personal information.
